https://www.excelsior.edu/policies/privacy-protection-policy/

MyExcelsior Sign In Coronavirus InfoResources for the Excelsior CommunityResources for Peer InstitutionsMilitaryAir Force & Air National GuardArmy & Army National GuardMarine CorpsMilitary Family MembersCoast GuardNavyVeteransAlumniPursue Your Next DegreeExcelsior Life (Blog)Excelsior College MagazineCareer CenterAlumni Events and WebinarsExcelsior CaresAlumni Leadership CouncilBecome an Alumni AmbassadorAlumni AwardsTranscript Request (login)MyExcelsior (login)Bookstore & MoreGive to the Scholarship FundsPay It ForwardGivingWays to GiveExcelsior College Annual FundsScholarship Endowment FundsOther Endowment FundsCorporate GivingDonor RecognitionDonate Online NowPay It ForwardPartnersCorporate, Association, and Government PartnersCommunity College and Other Academic PartnersMilitary PartnersVeteran PartnershipsTuition DeferralPartner Scholarship ProgramUpcoming Webinars
Request Info
Call Us
Apply / Enroll Areas of StudyBusinessBusiness UndergraduateAAS in Administrative and Management StudiesBPS in Business And ManagementBS in BusinessBusiness GraduateMBAMS in ManagementGraduate CertificateCannabis ControlApplication RequirementsUndergraduate & GraduateMilitary & Veterans Start HereInternational Students Start HereBusiness Career Training CoursesHealth SciencesHealth Sciences UndergraduateAS in Health SciencesBS in Health Care ManagementBS in Health SciencesHealth Sciences GraduateMS in Health SciencesMS in Health Care AdministrationGraduate CertificateCannabis ControlApplication RequirementsUndergraduate & GraduateMilitary & VeteransInternationalHealthcare Career Training CoursesLiberal ArtsLiberal Arts UndergraduateAS in Liberal ArtsBA in Liberal ArtsBS in HistoryBS in Liberal ArtsBS in Natural SciencesBS in PsychologyBS in Social SciencesApplication RequirementsUndergraduateMilitary & VeteransInternationalCareer and Professional Skills Training CoursesNursingNursing UndergraduateAAS in NursingAS in NursingRN to BS in NursingNursing GraduateRN to MS in Nursing EducationRN to MS in Nursing InformaticsRN to MS in Nursing Leadership and Administration of Health Care SystemsMS in Nursing EducationMS in Nursing InformaticsMS in Nursing Leadership and Administration of Health Care SystemsApplication RequirementsAssociateBachelor’sMaster’sMilitary & VeteransInternationalCareer and Professional Skills Training CoursesPublic ServicePublic Service UndergraduateAS in Criminal JusticeBS in Criminal JusticeBS in Homeland Security and Emergency ManagementBS in Military LeadershipBS in National SecurityPublic Service GraduateMaster of Public Administration (MPA)MS in Criminal JusticeGraduate CertificateCannabis ControlApplication RequirementsUndergraduate & GraduateMilitary & VeteransInternationalCareer and Professional Skills Training CoursesTechnologyTechnology UndergraduateAAS in Technical StudiesBPS in Technology ManagementBS in CybersecurityBS in Electrical Engineering TechnologyBS in Information TechnologyBS in Nuclear Engineering TechnologyTechnology GraduateMS in CybersecurityApplication RequirementsUndergraduate & GraduateMilitary & VeteransInternationalTechnology Career Training CoursesCourses & ExamsOnline Course CatalogEnrolled Student Course RegistrationVisiting Student Course RegistrationNoncredit CoursesCareer and Professional Skills TrainingCredit by ExamHow Credit By Exam WorksChoose Your ExamRegister for ExamsPrepare for Your ExamsTransfer Your UExcel® creditsCredit By Exam Content GuidesExcelsior College Exams in NursingAdmissionsAdmissions OverviewAcademic CalendarPrior Learning CreditWhere to Send Your TranscriptsEnrollment OptionsPursue Your Next DegreeApplication RequirementsBusinessHealth SciencesLiberal ArtsNursingPublic ServiceTechnologyMilitary & Veterans Start HereInternational Students Start HereTuition and AidTuitionUndergraduate TuitionGraduate TuitionMilitary TuitionVeteran TuitionEstimate Your Tuition and Time to CompletionFinancial AidFederal Financial AidSteps to Apply for Financial AidNY State Financial Aid for ResidentsExcelsior College ScholarshipsGrant and Private Loan OpportunitiesResourcesDocuments and FormsPayment PlansResourcesResources & ServicesCareer DevelopmentBookstore & MoreExcelsior College LibraryAcademic CalendarOnline Writing LabOnline Reading LabAccessibility ServicesTech SupportTranscript RequestsOnline Transcript Request for Students and AlumniOneTranscript® Service for Non-Excelsior StudentsMilitary and Veteran ResourcesCenter for Military and Veteran EducationVeterans CenterProgram CatalogsCatalogsStart With More CreditStart With More CreditTransfer Credits for CoursesCredit by ExamCredit for IT Certifications, Training, and ExamsCredit for Military ExperienceCredit for Health Care CredentialsCredit for Nursing Certifications and LicensesCredit for Criminal Justice TrainingCredit for FEMA Training and PMP CertificationCredit By PortfolioAboutInstitutional InformationAbout Excelsior CollegeGeneral Education Career CompetenciesDiversity, Equity and InclusionAccreditationsCommencementOur Students and GraduatesLeadershipContact InformationJobs at ExcelsiorMedia and PublicationsLife at Excelsior College BlogExcelsior College MagazineMedia KitAcademic Program CatalogsStudent Policy HandbookTransparencyAcademic TransparencyAdministrative TransparencyRegulatory TransparencyCoronavirus InfoResources for the Excelsior CommunityResources for Peer InstitutionsSearchsearch No Application Fee until December 31 - Apply Today
Request Info
Apply
Call Us
CLOSE
Call UsFor general inquiries, Admissions, Office of Registration and Records, Examinations Test Administration Office, and the Center for Military and Veteran Education:
1.888.647.2388 Financial Aid Office 1.518.464.8501International Students 1.518.464.8501TDD 1.518.464.8501
CLOSE
Frequently Asked QuestionsHow many credits can I transfer?How much is tuition?How do I apply?How do I request a transcript online?How do I submit the TEAS test results?What is OneTranscript and how does it work?Is my employer an Excelsior College Partner? Frequently Asked QuestionsHow many credits can I transfer?How much is tuition?How do I apply?How do I request a transcript online?How do I submit the TEAS test results?What is OneTranscript and how does it work?Is my employer an Excelsior College Partner?
PoliciesPoliciesPoliciesStudent PoliciesFaculty PoliciesPrivacy Protection PolicyFERPA and Access to Student RecordsSexual Harassment PolicyIntellectual Property PolicyConsumer Complaint ProcessCampus Security ReportNetiquettePoliciesPrivacy Protection PolicyThis policy applies to all parties (staff, faculty, students, alumni, etc.) who provide any amount or type of personal data to Excelsior College (“Excelsior” or “College”).Personal data includes but is not limited to data subject’s name, home address, email address, social security number, student identification number, photo, Internet Protocol (IP) address, a cookie identifier, transcripts, employment records, etc.Statement of PolicyThe use of our website is conditioned upon adherence to our terms of use and privacy policy.  This policy refers to our commitment to treat personal data of all parties with appropriate care.Personal Data Collected by ExcelsiorWhen you access our website, you may voluntarily give personal data to us so we can provide you with requested information or services. Some examples are: your name, address, phone number, and email address. You can always opt not to provide such information to us. However, we may not be able to communicate with you if you choose to opt out.In addition, during your interaction with our website, other personal data about your usage of the site is collected automatically, such as: top viewed and visited pages and links on our web site, top entry and exit points, number of form completions, time spent on pages, top downloads, top keywords used offsite to lead customers to our website, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, information collected via cookies (see below), device event information such as system activity, crashes, hardware settings, browser type, etc.What are cookies? Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers we transfer to your computer or mobile device through your internet browser to recognize you as a return user of our site. The information we collect is used to make our website and services we provide more customized and beneficial to you.You may set your internet browser to block all cookies including ours. The “help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will direct you on how to enable or disable cookies. However, some online services will not work if cookies are disabled.After you opt in and acknowledge that you are accepting the use of our cookies, your continued use of our website is your consent to the collection of this data for the purposes outlined above unless and until you decide to opt out.How Excelsior Uses the Information It CollectsExcelsior uses the information we collect to enhance our website and the services we provide to you. Excelsior does not share, sell, rent or trade personal data to third parties for their promotional purposes. Excelsior does share limited information with companies that perform work on our behalf. These companies are required to keep this information confidential and to use it strictly for authorized business purposes in accordance with Excelsior College policies and applicable laws and regulations.Excelsior may release personal information when we believe in good faith that it is necessary for us to comply with the law or for the safety of our employees, our customers, or others.Excelsior also shares aggregate information for regulatory or governmental reporting purposes.Excelsior contracts with third parties to engage in targeted online advertising. Third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect and receive information from Excelsior’s website. Further, Excelsior may use information collected to provide measurement services and target ads and may share information in connection with website retargeting. You may opt out of the collection and use of information for use in ad targeting.Email and Text Communications from ExcelsiorExcelsior often uses email communications to update you about new programs or services that may be of interest to you. Each such email communication contains instructions on how to opt out of receiving future communications. Excelsior receives a confirmation when you open and/or interact with an email from us if your system permits. We use this information to ensure that future communications with you are as helpful and useful as possible.Excelsior uses texting to send messages that are timely and relevant but only if you opt in to receiving texts from us. Even if you do opt in to accepting texts from us, you may opt out at any time. However, by opting out you may not receive helpful information that is important to you in a prompt manner.In its communications, the College adheres to the requirements of the Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act of 2003 (CAN-SPAM Act), the Telephone Consumer Protection Act (TCPA), and other applicable laws and regulations.Updating Your InformationIf you believe that any information Excelsior has collected about you is inaccurate or which you would like removed from our system, you may be able to change it yourself using the MyProfile (login required) application. You can also use MyProfile to opt out of electronic mail communications. Otherwise, contact the Office of the Registrar to make any changes.Excelsior uses tools to track aggregate data on the use of our website. Excelsior uses cookies to inform, optimize, and show you ads most relevant to your interests based on your past visits to our website. Third-party vendors may show you Excelsior ads on sites you visit across the Internet. After you opt-in and acknowledge that you accept use of our cookies, your continued use of our website is your consent to the collection of this data for the purposes stated in this policy until you opt out.Data SecurityExcelsior uses information technology industry best practices to ensure that all personal data is kept secure from unauthorized access and from improper use by authorized users.Data BreachesData breaches, whether caused through human error or malicious intent, will be reported to the chief technology officer, or designee, for investigation and reporting, as appropriate. Once a breach has been confirmed, designated staff will take appropriate steps, as outlined in the Excelsior College Crisis Management Plan. Any questions about the College’s data breach reporting process should be directed to the chief technology officer, or designee; via email to cto@excelsior.edu.Use of Social MediaWhen customers are interacting with Excelsior’s staff, students, and alumni or accessing content via social media such as Facebook, Twitter, etc., users should be aware that they are subject to the terms of use of these services. Customers should read and fully understand the privacy policies and terms of use of these services before accessing them.Links to Third-Party Content or WebsitesExcelsior bears no responsibility for the accuracy of third-party or user-generated content posted on its website and the opinions expressed by third parties and/or users are not necessarily those of the College or its employees. If the College receives a complaint regarding third-party or user-generated content on its website, the College will follow the procedures required by the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA).When you are on our site you may link to other websites and other websites may contain links to the College’s site. These other websites are not under Excelsior’s control and such links do not necessarily constitute an endorsement of those sites or the services offered by them. Excelsior is not responsible for the privacy policy, security practices, or content of such third-party websites.Amendment of Excelsior’s Privacy PolicyExcelsior reserves the right to amend this policy at any time without notice. Any questions about this policy should be directed to the chief technology officer, or designee, via email to cto@excelsior.edu.Use of Information and MaterialThe information and material contained on this site, and the terms, conditions, and descriptions that appear, are subject to change at any time without notice. Any information or material on this site may be downloaded for review provided the user does so for their individual, non-commercial use. Such information or material may not be otherwise copied, edited, linked with, or used, in any other website, visual, print, or broadcast medium, without the express permission of the College.The European Union General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (GDPR)Pursuant to the GDPR, the College, in its capacity as Data Controller, provides this information for individual data subjects (staff, faculty, students, alumni, etc.) residing in the European Union (“EU”):The GDPR applies to personal data the College may collect and process, and may include a data subject’s name, home address, email address, social security number, student identification number, photo, Internet Protocol (IP) address, a cookie identifier, transcripts, employment records, etc.As a higher education institution, Excelsior College may collect and process personal data for the purposes of providing information or services to data subjects, including but not limited to:  admissions, advisement, billing, bookstore purchases/transactions, communications, contracts with third-party vendors, employment, delivery of instruction, enrollment, financial aid assistance, promoting degree programs of potential interest to data subjects, payroll, records retention, registration, social media platforms, transcripts, tuition assistance, tutoring, etc.Lawful Basis for Collecting and Processing Personal DataThe College has determined the categories listed below may apply when collecting and processing personal data:Consent: The data subject has given consent for the College to process his or her personal data for a specific purpose.Legitimate Interests: The processing is necessary for the College’s legitimate interests or the legitimate interests of a third party.Personal Data BreachesData breaches, whether caused through human error or malicious intent, will be reported to the College’s chief technology officer, who has been appointed as the governance and data protection officer for investigation and reporting, as appropriate. Any questions about the College’s data breach reporting process should be directed to the governance and data protection officer, or designee, via email to cto@excelsior.edu.Once a breach has been confirmed and it is determined that the breach poses a risk to an individual’s rights and freedoms, the governance and data protection officer will notify the supervisory authority without undue delay, but no later than 72 hours following confirmation of the data breach.Once a breach has been confirmed and it is determined that the breach poses a high risk to an individual’s rights and freedoms, the governance and data protection officer will also notify the individuals directly and without undue delay.Student Records RetentionThe Office of Registrar is responsible for providing a centralized imaging function for creation of the student’s electronic file and for maintaining, retrieving, and disposing of paper and electronic records. This is done in compliance with state and federal laws and the American Association of Collegiate Registrars and Admissions Officers (AACRAO) guidelines for the retention of student records.
We use cookies to ensure the best web experience possible.
You can learn more about how we use cookies in our Privacy Policy. By continuing to use this website, you consent to our usage of cookies in accordance with our Privacy Policy.Accept
